{
    "id": "0d604c41dbb443dc8992dfb328dd25fa",
    "title": "I'd Rather, Had Better, I Wish",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ........................... on Monday.",
            "description": "After would rather we use a past tense to refer to the present or future.",
            "answers": [
                "don't come",
                "didn't come",
                "wouldn't come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97dca5c4a233421e865385e34aa1a0fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'd rather you .................................. fight with me in public.",
            "description": "After would rather we use a past tense to refer to the present or future.",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't",
                "wouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "acefe0d027c74bd5a1d850e613e8787d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You'd better ............................. now before he gets angry.",
            "description": "After had better we use the infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "to leave",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e130942c6d394a5eb2efed0bcfeb2dc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I 'd rather you ............................. me with the housework.",
            "description": "After would rather we use a past tense to refer to the present or future.",
            "answers": [
                "help",
                "helped",
                "had helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "442a12773a7949b3ab9c7ab62697ed7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You'd better .................................. smoking.",
            "description": "After had better we use the infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "stop",
                "stopped",
                "to stop"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4087d012b5a478391c5169e3c2e7433"
        },
        {
            "question": "We'd better ................................... seats.",
            "description": "After had better we use the infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "reserve",
                "to reserve",
                "reserved"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf935a9efc044cefb95e192fbf2ba935"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ............................... there when they arrived.",
            "description": "We use a past perfect tense after wish to talk about the past.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "had been",
                "will be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efa312a320bc41229aae0c46c6fbe017"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ............................... like that.",
            "description": "We use a past perfect tense after wish to talk about the past.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't behave",
                "hadn't behaved",
                "don't behave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e8014b5541014665bf19a15d617289ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I .................................. out of school at",
            "description": "We use a past perfect tense after wish to talk about the past.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't drop",
                "wouldn't drop",
                "hadn't dropped"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8785cc87e45746558dd2131f6a8cabc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ................................... handsome.",
            "description": "We use a past tense after I wish with present or future meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f246ceb4c74142198b0a98f4c6bf3c53"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish that it ………………………….. stop raining soon.",
            "description": "We use a past tense after I wish with present or future meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "03b8801c81524f94bdd42a96b447714b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish dad ……………………… come soon.",
            "description": "We use would after wish to express our impatience or dissatisfaction with something.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6215237cb2984155a75ad84ded687552"
        }
    ]
}